digitalagencynetwork.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy

This Privacy Policy covers information we collect from users and visitors of our Website, located at https://digitalagencynetwork.com as owned and operated by DAN Global (UK) Limited. By accessing the Site, using any of the Services, or otherwise agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure and other handling of your information as described below.

You further agree to the terms contained in this Privacy Policy and any documents incorporated by reference, whether you are registered with Digital Agency Network (“Registered User or Agency”) or are simply browsing the Site. If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information collected on the Site, you should not use the Services and the Site.

Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information.

### 1\. Your Rights

When using our website and submitting personal data to us, you may have certain rights under the [General Data Protection Regulation](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-data-protection/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/) (GDPR) and other laws. Depending on the legal basis for processing your personal data, you may have some or all of the following rights:

 **The right to be informed:** You have the right to be informed about the personal data we collect from you, and how we process it.

 **The right of access:** You have the right to get confirmation that your personal data is being processed and have the ability to access your personal data.

 **The right to rectification:** You have the right to have your personal data corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete.

 **The right to erasure:** You have the right to request the removal or deletion of your personal data if there is no compelling reason for us to continue processing it.

 **The right to object:** You have the right to object to us processing your personal data.

### 2) What information do we collect?

You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.

 **Information You Provide to Us** : We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. The information we collect is clearly set out on the web page on which we collect it. In addition, we may collect your IP address and use cookies; please refer to Cookies section below.

When you register with us through the Site and become a Registered User, we collect your personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personally Identifiable Information“). Personally Identifiable Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone numbers, email address, business address, and intended usage of requested information, but does not include your credit card number or billing information.

We collect information about you so that we can personalise your experience and better respond to your individual needs, to improve our website generally, to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature and to send periodic emails.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **We collect your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways:**

 **a) Automatically Collected Information**  
When you use our Website, our servers automatically collect certain information that your web browser sends by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. These automated means may include Web Analytics information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type and language, platform type, landing pages, pages viewed, bounce rates, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and cookies that may identify your browser. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. This mentioned information is being collected when:

  * You enter and use our website and agree to accept cookies, some of these cookies may contain your Personally Identifiable Information.
  * If you buy products or services from us, we collect your first and last name, email address, phone number, and other information listed.
  * You submit a request to write for us we collect your first name, email address and samples of your work.

 **b) Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through the Web browser. Cookies enable the sites or service providers to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to identify the data about our site traffic and interaction so that we can personalize the content that you see on our Website and offer better site experiences. We may make agreements with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors.

By agreeing to accept our use of cookies, you are giving us, and third parties we partner with, permission to place, store, and access some or all the cookies described below on your computer:

Strictly Necessary Cookies  
These cookies are necessary for proper functioning of the website, such as displaying content, logging in, validating your session, responding to your request for services, and other functions.

Performance Cookies  
These cookies collect information about the use of the website, such as pages visited, traffic sources, users’ interests, content management, and other website measurements.

Functional Cookies  
These cookies enable the website to remember a user’s choices – such as their language, user name, and other personal choices – while using the website. They can also be used to deliver services, such as letting a user make a blog post, listen to audio, or watch videos on the website.

Media Cookies  
These cookies can be used to improve a website’s performance and provide special features and content. They can be placed by third parties who provide services to us or by our company.

Advertising or Targeting Cookies  
These cookies are usually placed and used by advertising companies to develop a profile of your browsing interests and serve advertisements on other websites that are related to your interests. You will see less advertising if you disable these cookies.

Session Cookies  
These cookies allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session. They may be used for a variety of purposes. Session cookies also permit users to be recognized as they navigate a website so that any item or page changes they make are remembered from page to page. Session cookies expire after a browser session; thus, they are not stored long term.

Persistent Cookies  
These cookies are stored on a user’s device in between browser sessions, which allows the user’s preferences or actions across a site to be remembered. Persistent cookies may be used for a variety of purposes, including remembering users’ choices and preferences when using a website or to target advertising to them.

We may also use cookies for:

  * Identifying the areas of our website that you have visited
  * Personalizing content that you see on our website
  * Our website analytics
  * Remarketing our products or services to you
  * Remembering your preferences, settings, and login details
  * Targeted advertising and serving ads relevant to your interests
  * Affiliate marketing
  * Allowing you to post comments
  * Allowing you to share content with social networks

If you are uncomfortable with the collection of data through the use of cookies, we recommend disabling this feature through your browser preferences.

 **c) Automatic Information & Log Data**  
We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website.

Through cookies and other automated means, Web servers may log information such as IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your device type, operating system type, mobile device identifier, browser type, domain, and other system settings, the name of your ISP or mobile carrier.

We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

 **d) Submitting a Resume or Employment Application**  
When submitting a resume or employment application we collect your first and last name, email address,region, city, date of birth and social profile links that you provide.

### 3\. How do we use your information?

We use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with Automatically Collected Information we receive to customize our Website.

We use the information we collect about you to establish your account and provide the Services; provide customized content to you; communicate with you through email and phone, send you emails to inform you about our features and services; promotional messages and web analytics data, provide feedback to third party businesses; and take action regarding unlawful or harmful activities, contact you with marketing and advertising that we believe may be of interest to you or provide our products and services you have requested or purchased from us.

 **a) Communications and Emails**  
When we communicate with you about our website, we will use the email address you provided when you registered as a member or user. We may also send you emails with promotional information about our website or offers from us or our affiliates unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change your contact preferences at any time through your account or by sending us an email with your request to: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#89e0e7efe6c9ede8e7eee5e6ebe8e5a7eae6e4)

 **b) Sharing Information With Affiliates and Other Third Parties**  
We do not sell, rent or trade your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **c) Sharing Information with Facebook and Google for Marketing Purposes**  
We may share your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) with third parties for similar audience marketing purposes. Similar audience marketing is also called lookalike audience marketing. The third parties we share your PII with for this type of marketing include Facebook and/or Google Analytics and/or Google Search Console, Google Adwords and/or any other Google tools. Using your PII, for similar audience marketing or lookalike audience marketing helps us find new audiences based on similar interests to yours. Your PII is only shared with Facebook and Google for this type of marketing. By using our website and agreeing to our privacy notice, you are giving your consent for your PII to be used for the marketing purposes described within this section.

 **d)** We use [Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device’s IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy). You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).

 **e) Retaining and Destroying Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
We retain information that we collect from you, once you become a DAN member after filling out the submission form, only for as long as we need it for legal, business, or tax purposes. Once the membership is expired, we maintain the PII you have submitted via submission form for 1 year and delete it unless membership renewal is requested.

 **f) Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
You can update your PII by contacting us using the contact information found at the end of this notice and we will help you. However, we may keep your PII as needed to enforce our agreements and to comply with any legal obligations.

 **g) Revoking Your Consent for Using Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
You have the right to revoke your consent for us to use your PII at any time. Such an optout will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates and business partners, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers that provide certain services for our business, such as computer system services, shipping, data management services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfil your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments, or as otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept. If you want to revoke your consent for us to use your PII, send us an email with your request to: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#85ecebe3eac5e1e4ebe2e9eae7e4e9abe6eae8)

 **h) Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties**  
If any postings you make on our website contain information about third parties, you must make sure you have permission to include that information in your posting. While we are not legally liable for the actions of our users, we will remove any postings about which we are notified, if such postings violate the privacy rights of others.

### 4\. Links to other websites

This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and the Services. The Site and the Services may contain links to other websites over which we have no control. These websites may have their own policies regarding privacy.

We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other websites which you access from this Site or through the Services. If you choose to visit an individual, a business or advertiser’s website by “clicking on” on a third party link our Website, located at https://digitalagencynetwork.com, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present an advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of any such third party’s privacy or information security policies or practices.

You access such linked Websites at your own risk. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of those individual websites to see how the operators of those third-party websites will utilize your personal information. The information you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

### 5\. Security

The security of your information is very important to us, but please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. As a result, whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you send to us, and you do so at your own risk.

You should report any security violations to us at this email address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#cda4a3aba28da9aca3aaa1a2afaca1e3aea2a0)

Our Email Policy: You can always opt out of receiving further email correspondence from us or our affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business, or if our company files for bankruptcy.

If you receive an email that appears to be from DAN Global or Digital Agency Network that requests personal information (such as your credit card, login, or password), or that asks you to verify or confirm your account or other personal information by clicking on a link, that email was likely to have been sent by someone trying to unlawfully obtain your information. We do not ask for this type of information in an email. Do not provide the information or click on the link. Please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e58c8b838aa581848b82898a878489cb868a88) if you get an email like this.

### 6\. Updates to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine and will be identified at the top of the Privacy Policy page of the Site by its Effective Date.

Please review the changes carefully. If you disagree with the Privacy Policy, you must stop using the Services and the Site.

### 7\. How to contact us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or your privacy in connection with your use of the Site or any general questions, you may call us on [+44 20 3008 8065](tel:+44 20 3008 8065) or send email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b3daddd5dcf3d7d2ddd4dfdcd1d2df9dd0dcde)
